У багатьох людей був сонний параліч, але ми не називаємо їх "хворими."
Але...
Гм... можливо не так багато людей відчували саме те що відчувала ти.
Але в будь - якому разі, я не думаю що тебе слід називати "хворою" тільки через те що ти відчуваєш.
Молоді та вразливі люди можуть відчувати багато дивних речей.
Але мені страшно, я ненавиджу це.
Що такого страшного було у твоєму сні?
Я починаю відчувати що я нікому не потрібна.
Ти "нікому не потрібна"?
Я відчуваю як мені наказують повертатися тому що я нікому не потрібна.
Повертатися? Повертатися куди?
До себе.
Гм. Це важко зрозуміти. Ти хочеш повернутися до себе?
Не знаю. Але я відчуваю що є інша я, вона торкається мого тіла, розриваючи його на частини
(Перебиваючи) І це болісно?
Це не болісно, скоріш лячно.
I see. Does this happen when you’re asleep?
Напевно.
Probably? This happens sometimes when you’re not dreaming?
Я не знаю.
Sometimes it happens when I’m all by myself, and sometimes when I’m talking to my friends.
Tell me what happens when you’re not alone. This happens when you’re just having conversations?
Yes. While I’m just talking, it suddenly...
How do you notice it? Do your friends call out to you?
Suddenly...
Is there something that triggers it?
I was afraid, and I felt better after staying motionless for a while.
Можеш пояснити що ти відчувала або що ти бачила? Можеш намалювати це?
Ні, не можу.
Розумію... Ох!
Нам потрібно закінчувати.
Вибач, Лейн.
I have to go out and take care of some things today.
I’m sorry to have to stop right in the middle of a conversation.
But it’s good for now that you can’t see these things.
I think that what you experience is probably similar to sleep paralysis.
I’ll do some research on it until next month.
That’ll be my homework.
Your homework will be keeping a diary.
A diary?
I want you to write about the things you did during the day, and what you thought about.
You don’t have to show it to me.
Just write what you want.
I used to keep a diary when I was your age.
But...
You don't want to?
It can be really interesting to look back on the things you write in your diary.
We can be forgetful, so it can help you remember things, too.
That will cure me?
Hmm.
That probably doesn’t have anything to do with it.
At least it's good for you.
I’ll explain more carefully next month.
I don’t mind if you don’t want to keep a diary.
I went and bought you a diary book, though.
See?
It’s cute, isn’t it?
I found it when I went shopping last week, and I thought it would be a nice present for you.
Дякую.
But don’t force yourself.
You don't have to keep a diary just because I bought you one.
Feel free to write in the diary if you want to, though.
Well I guess we’ll wrap it up, then.
Make sure you’re not forgetting anything.
I’ll walk out to the gate with you.